With a probability of 10% for each unit of luck (but not more than 50%), the hero will be returned all the mana spent on casting the spell.
After casting spells, there is a 50% chance to return 20% * mana luck. The skill cannot work more than 2 times in a row, and also not work more than 2 times in a row; 3rd attempt
necessarily work (after 2 failures) or not work (after 2 operations). This counter is unique for each player.