This creature has a chance to frighten a target and its neighbors when attacking (small creatures are more disposed to fear). If successful the attacker gets +1 to its Morale and +10% to its Health. The Roar has a chance to frighten the enemies located on the 6 adjacent front tiles of the Whitebear Rider. Small creature's chance to be frightened is doubled. The bonus for frightening at least one enemy lasts 2 turns.