All the Summoning Magic spells of the first to third circles cast by the enemy are decreased by two mastery levels (Expert to Basic, Advanced to None, Basic becomes None and gets a -25% penalty to spellpower). The spellpower of spells cast initially without regard of mastery level of magic is decreased by 50%. The fourth and fifth circle spells cast by the enemy are decreased by one mastery level.