Finding itself under an area spell of Destruction Magic together with any friendly stacks, this creature assumes some of the damage that would normally go to the friendly units. Half of the damage absorbed is converted to heal points.(Doesn't apply to Armageddon spell). The Magnetic Golems redirect 9% per every 10 units in their stack of the damage to themselves. The damage is then actually converted to healing by their Enchanted Armor ability.