The High Druids of Irollan know all the most important secrets of Elven magic. They are capable of stopping an entire army in its tracks if it should reach as far as the edge of the Great Forest. And their ability to transfer some of their magical powers to the Rangers who lead them can often prove invaluable on the battle field.
<br>
<color=d4ac2b>Caster:
<color=999999>Endurance <color=d4ac2b>(advanced)