After surviving a grueling ordeal of penance upon the Dead Steppe, the Earth Daughter can call upon her mastery of the Orc's Blood Rage and her bonds with Mother Earth to launch savage melee attacks against which her enemies cannot retaliate. In order to maximize the damage she does, an Earth Daughter can sacrifice Goblins to improve both her Blood Rage and her mana.
<br>
<color=d4ac2b>Caster:
<color=999999>Slow <color=d4ac2b>(advanced)
<color=999999>Haste <color=d4ac2b>(advanced)