The Inquisitors are the keepers of the true faith of Elrath, the Holy Dragon of Light. As such they fight fiercely against non-believers and enemies of the Church. On the battlefield Inquisitors do not enter the melee, but rather summon the wrath of Elrath on enemy troops while protecting their own with support spells.
<br>
<color=d4ac2b>Caster:
<color=999999>Haste <color=d4ac2b>(advanced)
<color=999999>Divine Strength <color=d4ac2b>(advanced)
<color=999999>Endurance <color=d4ac2b>(advanced)