The white wings of this angel have long been tainted by the blood of its enemies, and its scarlet attire serves as a warning to any who believe all angels are benevolent creatures. Seraphs exist not as saviours of the innocent, but as the scourge of their enemies.
<br>
<color=d4ac2b>Caster:
<color=999999>Righteous Might <color=d4ac2b>(expert)
<color=999999>Divine Vengeance <color=d4ac2b>(basic)