Guided by a higher force, the Zealots are the scourge of all those who refuse to bow to Elrath. Embracing the "smiting" aspect of the Light, they prefer not to preach, but to punish the enemy and remove the blessing (f=2.0). They cannot be diverted from their holy crusade, and all pleas for mercy are pointless.
<br>
<color=d4ac2b>Caster:
<color=999999>Cleansing <color=d4ac2b>(advanced)
<color=999999>Righteous Might <color=d4ac2b>(advanced)