These gargantuan monsters are so wild and fierce that even the orcs are afraid of them. When an Untamed Cyclops flies into a rage it can no longer control its actions and is even known to destroy goblins, which are a favorite delicacy. The Cyclops' strength is so great and stunning (f=1.0), and its huge club so mighty that they are often deployed as siege machines to destroy gates, towers or city ramparts. And woe betides any poor guard who falls into the Cyclops' clutches.