Doing battle with a Mauler is an extremely thankless and exhausting task. These warriors are born fighters, and there is nothing they desire more than to be in the thick a battle, where the blood of the enemy flows in rivers. As soon as they go into battle Maulers are transformed into pure killing machines. Armed with maces, and able to move at great speed, they are guaranteed to shed plenty of enemy blood. And where other fighters would manage just a single blow, the Mauler can deliver two (f=1.0), meaning that the level of harm it inflicts on his foe is far greater.