Когда существо атакует противника, существует шанс, что оно его ослепит на 1.6 хода. Ослепшие существа не могут двигаться или нападать, но обретут зрение, если будут атакованы. Способность не действует против нежити, элементалей и механических существ.

When this creature attacks the enemy, there is a chance that it will blind it in addition to inflicting regular damage. Blinded creatures cannot move or attack, but regain sight if attacked. Вuration of blinding - 1.6 turns. 
The ability does not work against undead, elementals and mechanical creatures.