The hero receives special combat ability to punish the target enemy creature with a powerful Mark of the Damned if that creature is about to attack, retaliate, or cast any spell. Once declared, Mark of the Damned is active until the end of combat. Should target creature remain idle or move without attacking, the mark will not be performed. When calculating the damage inflicted, the hero's level increases by +3. The hero spends only half of his turn using this skill.