Sprites are close relatives of the Pixies who live in the higher branches of the Kersyl trees. Their small size and speed allow them to attack more than one creature and to retreat before retaliation is possible. Also, the Sprites' affinity with the woods is such that they can call upon Nature's powers to cast spells in combat.
<br>
<color=d4ac2b>Caster:
<color=999999>Wasp Swarm <color=d4ac2b>(null)
<color=999999>Cleansing <color=d4ac2b>(advanced)