Each time when a morale effect is triggered with any of the creatures in the hero's army, the hero moves 10% forward along the ATB bar. Accordingly, when a negative morale effect is triggered, the hero moves 10% back.
For Necromancer: The main effect works on the Phoenix and the Elementals in the hero's army, but also when an enemy creature dies, a necromancer or a random creature in the hero's army, including the summoned ones, instantly gets a move.