Makes war machines more effective overall. The number of Hit Points of all War Machines increases by +300. The Catapult damage increases and there is a 50% chance of destroying the target. The healing power of the First Aid Tent is increasing to 200 HP. The Ammo Cart gets the ability to increase the attack of shooters in the hero's army by +3. The hero gets all kinds of War Machines before the battle.