Once per combat the Succubus is able to gain control over any enemy creature that is not immune to Mind Control. The ability's duration depends on the difference in power between the Seducers and their victims, ranging from 4 turns (target is four times as weak as the Succubi) to the point where it can't be used (target is four times as strong as the Succubi). The Succubus' ATB value does not increase for the time of the effect's duration. Activated ability.